(Leonard:)Wolowitz sent his in two days ago.
(Penny:)-Really, let it go.
-Look, maybe it is a long shot,
(Leonard:)but sometimes long shots happen.
(Leonard:)Luke Skywalker was only given one
chance to destroy the Death Star.
(Leonard:)He had to get a torpedo
into an exhaust port
(Leonard:)that was only two meters wide,
but with the help of The Force, he--
(Leonard:)Wow, I can feel you
hating me right now.
(Stuart:)How about that lady
in the sweat suit, speed-walking?
(Raj:)Yeah, she seems friendly
and easy to...
(Raj:)Never mind, she's gone.
(Raj:)Maybe talking
to people is too hard.
(Stuart:)We could go over to that department
store, practice on the mannequins.
(Penny:)I don't know.
They're dressed very stylishly.
(Raj:)They're probably stuck-up.
(Raj:)This is ridiculous.
(Raj:)The next person that walks by,
no matter who it is, they're the one.